MUHAMMAD MUNEEB AMJAD

Rawalpindi, Pakistan

muneebamjad302@gmail.com 03145149455

I am passionate software engineer with 1+ years of professional experience in web development process for small to medium-sized companies. Demonstrated excellent skills in HTML, Bootstrap, jQuery, Laravel, REST and JSON etc. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2020 - APRIL 2021

PHP/LARAVEL DEVELOPER, E2E SOLUTIONS

I worked as Laravel Developer, my responsibility was to add new feature to the existing website and remove bugs from the website.

APRIL 2021 – JUN 2021

PHP/LARAVEL DEVELOPER, SUBLIME LOGICS

I worked as Laravel full stack developer. I handled multiple websites like adding new features, removes bugs, code optimization etc.

JULY 2021 - TO - (PRESENT)

PHP/LARAVEL DEVELOPER, FORTE SOLUTIONS LLC

I worked as Laravel full stack developer. I made two websites from scratch one is for online shopping (buy and sell things) other one is for car wash and car rent management.

EDUCATION

2013

MATRIC, F. G. BOYS HIGH SCHOOL, R.A BAZAR, RAWALPINDI

Biology

2014-2016

ICS, GLOBAL COLLEGE OF SCIENCES, RAWALPINDI CANTT

Computer Science

2016-2020

BSCS, PIR MEHR ALI SHAH ARID AGRICULTURE UNIVERSITY, RAWALPINDI

Computer Science

SKILLS

Web Development

React.js

- Web programming
- Front End technologies (Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery React.js etc.)
- Backend technologies (Laravel, Php, payment gateways)
- API, REST API etc.

- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PHP
- Git, GitHub, bitbucket
- JSON

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Even outside of work, I spend much of my time improving my skills, explore new technologies and developing personal applications. When not programming, I also enjoy snooker and staying active outdoors, as well as playing different type of games etc.